We are the Roseguard Imperial Knights.
We heard a hero was headed into this cave and hurried here.
Oh, that's so.
The knights under the command of Captain Rosalie are engaging the Demon Lord's forces at Olga Fortress.
We ask that you come with us.
Okay.
We did come here to save the world after all.
So let's get going.
The rumors are true.
It's like having a hundred more men.
Is there anybody in this world who doesn't need my help?
I was hoping for like five seconds of downtime.
We will gladly lead you all the way to Olga Fortress.
I'd rather you didn't.
Just tell me what direction it's in.
North by Northwest.
Oh, he really can fly.
No ordinary mortal can do that.
That's why heroes are better than us.
I believe he can bring down Beelbub.
Who's this Beelbub you're talking about?
A demon that looks like a giant fly.
A swarm of those disgusting creatures led by Beelbub is causing massive casualties at Olga Fortress.
So we're in for midair combat.
We'll do a little recon first.
Tater tots on me.
Rista, grab the other one, would you?
No problem.
Oh, wow.
Being able to fly with you is incredible, Master.
Something doesn't look right up ahead.
Huh?
Maybe it's a rain cloud?
That's a huge swarm of flies.
Gross.
Three to four hundred of those flying poop eaters.
All over level 30.
So the phoenix is out.
Let's stay back and see what happens.
Yeah, I'm good with that plan.
Bow down before us, humans.
Tremble at the overwhelming might of the Demon Lord's airborne shock troops.
The aerial assault flies.
I'm thinking that must be the boss bug.
His ability stats kind of suck, so he's not a heavenly king.
That speed rating is kind of out of control, though.
He disgusts me.
I mean, like, how can he talk with that mouth?
I don't even want to know.
How does that help us counteract his stupid fast feet?
Look over there.
Those Rose Guard soldiers are being targeted.
Release!
It looks like even the minion flies all have pretty decent evasive skills as well.
Now, it's time for something I like to call reverse fireworks.
Say what now?
I don't get it.
I was thinking about calling them Beelbub's blood bombs, but that seems corny.
Hmm.
There's no fire, but you get the idea.
Now, where's that hero?
Is this not enough to draw him out?
I can kill more.
I can do this all day.
Am I right?
I wondered why the fortress hadn't fallen, but he basically just told us what was up,
so that's helpful.
I love it when they just tell us like that.
Master, are we going to stand around here and watch, or are we going to swat these flies?
Slow your roll, Turbo.
Normal flies move faster than the blink of an eye, and these are some kind of demon flies,
so they probably move unbelievably quickly.
Now's not the time to act.
Elulu, stay behind me, okay?
Okay?
Oh, thank goodness!
You've come at last!
Listen up, soldiers!
The hero and goddess have finally arrived to save our world!
Now stand tall!
Prepare to storm the demon's lair!
Captain Rosalie, please calm yourself.
First, we need to regroup and let the men rest.
We can rest only after we've avenged our fallen brothers in arms.
I know the thirst for blood vengeance well, but you must realize the situation we're in.
Our remaining soldiers are beyond exhausted.
Besides, the hero's just barely arrived.
I suppose you have a point, Carlo.
Let's head back to the fortress.
There we can discuss a strategy to finally defeat these flies with our hero.
Captain Rosalie!
However, once that meeting is done, we're heading back out.
That is an order, you understand?
What are you waiting for?
Move it!
Yes, ma'am!
Wow, that place is massive!
Olga Fortress is at a strategic location on the Imperial border.
In addition to strong walls, the garrison's elite archers are stationed up in the ramparts.
Well, those flies could definitely break through if they wanted.
Clearly, their objective was to lure you here.
They wouldn't go any further than the fortress.
But even if they did, the Empire is protected by the Great War Master.
Who's that?
His name really says it all.
He's the greatest living warrior in Gaea Brande.
Yeah, if that were true, he could be saving the world instead of me.
I don't buy the hype.
Forgive me, but present company excluded.
The War Master's absolutely, without a doubt, the mightiest man to ever walk this land.
However, he can't leave the capital.
Captain Rosalie, must you be on the battlefront?
You are next in line to the Imperial Throne, after all!
Which is why I should be in harm's way.
I'm my father's daughter.
A true warrior.
Um, excuse me.
They're here.
The hero and his courageous party have now arrived.
Oh, your greatness is inspiring.
We do appreciate your help.
Come and have a seat.
So, without further ado, we must formulate a strategy at once to eliminate these flies.
Slow down, big guy.
I would like to guarantee our safety first.
One of the Demon Lord's henchmen could be right here with us in disguise.
Wait, do you think so?
All I'm saying is the possibility exists.
Well, I suppose there's a remote chance.
Besides, even if the enemy's not here, they could have planted a bomb to blow us all to hell.
There's a bomb in here?
All I'm saying is the possibility exists.
Yes, I suppose it does.
But even if there's not, I'm almost positive someone's listening in on this meeting.
Carlo, search the ceiling now!
Right!
Sir, 23 soldiers have searched high and low, but the entire area above this room is not only empty, but remarkably clean.
There's no sign of an intruder, sir.
Huh?
All I said was the possibility exists.
I've had enough of this!
What's more than just a possibility is we are not getting any fighting done!
We don't even need to strategize.
The hero and I will stand at the fore and charge into the creature's lair!
That's that!
But Captain Rosalie, we can't be!
She's right.
Huh?
Oh!
So you agree we should charge in?
Don't put words in my mouth.
What I agree with is this meeting is totally pointless.
I know what my next course of action needs to be.
So what do you plan to do?
To leave.
Huh?
Ah!
I'm gonna go back to the Divine Room.
Of course that's it.
A classic Sia move.
In here I was getting excited to start an adventure.
This is utterly ridiculous!
You're kidding, right?
I'm never kidding.
It's not my style.
You're seriously going to abandon us?
Cut the drama.
I'm just leaving.
But why?
Makes no sense.
He's chicken?
Well, he's not a hero.
Everyone relax.
I speak Sia.
He doesn't mean going off to train for long.
Probably no more than three days.
What the hell?
But the fortress will be destroyed at that time.
No, listen.
In the Divine Realm, three days is like an hour or so.
That's not too unreasonable.
But why would you even need to train for this fight?
I saw the goddess's wings with my own two eyes.
If you can already fly, you're ready.
Huh?
Who, me?
Goddesses don't fight.
They only support.
Oh, is he actually sticking up for me?
But don't get me wrong.
She's completely useless.
She just kind of floats like a balloon.
Now that I think about it, a balloon would be more capable.
Hey, I ought to punch your balloons!
Blind's no big deal.
I can do that.
Oh, is that so?
That doesn't make us less screwed.
Look, I was watching the battle earlier.
Wait.
What did you say?
You were watching?
While my soldiers were being slaughtered, you stood there and watched them die?
No, that's not true.
We wanted to help, but at the time it was just too late.
It's not about timing.
It's about helping or not helping.
I want to know if the hero saw what happened and did nothing to help.
That's a dumb question if you ask me.
If nothing will help, why would I do anything?
My men were murdered by demons.
You're a hero.
Doesn't that affect you?
What would change if it did?
Best thing to do was not get freaked out.
Stay calm and keep my guard up.
This hero is hopeless.
By definition, a hero is supposed to be brave.
But you are not a hero.
You're just a mopey coward.
Rosalie!
I know Seiya can come off as an unfeeling jerk who's afraid to get his hands dirty.
But that's how we've made it this far.
He'll kill those demon flies, but only when he knows he's ready.
So would you please just be patient?
This training will only take an hour.
And why should I?
Valid question.
Over a hundred of my men were popped like grapes.
Have some empathy.
I know it's a horrible thing to go through, but...
You can't know how precious life truly is because you don't have to fear death.
Since you're a goddess, it will literally never happen to you.
He kind of got me there.
So don't speak to me on matters of life and death.
You're not exactly coming from some kind of moral high ground, lady.
Say what?
Your men didn't get killed by accident.
All that stuff is on you.
If you had been able to come up with a strategy that didn't suck, they'd still be alive right now.
You scum!
You better take that back!
We should kill you!
Wow, time out!
Ziya, in what kind of world is hitting a woman ever okay?
You need to get down on your knees and beg or not to kill you now!
How dare you!
Ow!
Oh, you bastard!
You slept like a girl!
Oh, you'll pay for this!
Is there no shred of feminism in this day and age?
I knew he was kind of old-fashioned, but this is the bad kind!
All right, that's it!
You are dead!
I'll slice you to pieces!
Captain Rosalie, control yourself!
You're a fraud!
You are not a hero!
You're just a jerk face!
Apologize, you cape man!
Nope, she was coming in hard, bro.
Look at her!
You made her cry!
I know it!
I'm not crying!
You're crying!
The way that I see it, she should be apologizing to me.
The way I see it, you're an embarrassment to men and heroes, so apologize!
I don't need a stupid hero!
Ziya, shut up!
I'll go take care of them myself!
You do have incredibly high strength for a human.
The War Master may be your father, but I guess ability ratings aren't genetic.
You're just gonna get yourself killed.
She's starting to growl like a dog!
Is she gonna turn into a werewolf?
I think she's rabid, so leave her alone.
Hey, Master, are you sure you shouldn't apologize?
I'm sorry, but I don't do apologies.
Open a portal.
Let's go.
Uh, uh, sure.
Yeah, geez, that rally!
Is she a dog?
Okay, find our happy place!
We're leaving, but we'll be back in an hour!
Try not to bite anyone while we're gone!
I know you, um, have your ways, but don't ever do anything like that again!
There's no excuse!
I was scared you were gonna kill each other!
Well, that slapping was pretty intense.
I couldn't stop myself.
It's like all of that crap that she was spewing triggered my slap button.
Don't care.
The way she thinks is BS.
How bent on moving forward when there's no chance of winning.
Besides the casualties, it makes you look like an idiot.
Hmm.
Yeah, it's pretty much the exact opposite approach from how you like to do everything.
So, uh, you feel like taking a little breather?
Great.
Another dumb question.
I figured out how to deal with that demon bug infestation.
Well, if you need one of the gods around here to help you with something, I can hook you up.
Like the god of Patriot's surface-to-air missiles?
What?
There's no god for that!
How about the god of guns?
We might actually have one of those somewhere.
But although Gabriente has a lot of ways to kill, there are no guns.
If we're the only ones with guns, we win.
Listen, Saya, it's just not gonna happen!
Guns literally do not exist there!
Well, if the guns and Patriot missiles are out...
...that leaves us with bows.
Great!
Because I know the goddess of archery.
She's in the verdant forest, which is a little ways from here.
Cool.
Let's go.
Maybe she can teach me something.
Hmm!
She's practicing right up ahead!
Please pardon the interruption, Metis.
Oh, Ristarte, I don't see you here often.
Is there something I can help you with today?
Well, I was telling my hero friend here about your amazing skill as an archer,
and we were hoping you wouldn't mind sharing a few tips with him to up his game.
You're supposed to be the best, so how many arrows can you shoot at once?
Ever heard of buttering someone at first?
It isn't really possible to shoot more than one arrow at a time,
but I can shoot in quick succession to mimic simultaneous fire.
Shining arrow.
That was so fast, I bet the tree never even saw it coming!
After centuries of training, seven quick shots is my limit.
Just seven shots?
How about hitting something that actually moves?
Do you think you'd miss?
Um, no.
That would never happen.
Really?
I wouldn't be the goddess of archery if I missed.
Unfortunately, that kind of speed and precision is impossible for humans like you.
Yeah, we'll see. Why don't you teach me a thing or two first?
Before we begin, you need to be able to use a magic bow.
If that proves to be too much, there are other types of lessons I'd love to teach you, personally.
Send me what I think it means!
I just want to learn how to use the bow.
Elulu, you know how to use fire arrow, don't you? Teach it to me.
You're good at a lot of things, Ziya, but I don't know if you can just pick it up just like that!
Just do it, okay?
The first step is to stretch out your left hand and visualize a flaming magic bow in it.
Like this?
Now picture an arrow in your right hand.
You're going too fast!
But the next step is really the toughest part of the whole process.
Hitting the target is where all of the skills start to come in!
That was easy.
Well, for you, maybe.
My word, you are surprisingly quick to catch on.
I understand why she chose you.
I'd be happy to start training you right away.
Well, there goes my dignity.
Don't let it bother you.
That guy's a freak of nature.
Well, since we're waiting on him, how do you suggest we pass the time?
What did Ziya tell you?
You kids can go to the cafeteria and eat candy or whatever the hell you do.
Sounds like him.
I don't want to just sit around, so could you introduce me to a god who'll help me get stronger?
Yeah, I don't mind finding someone for you.
Do you want one, too?
Nah, not today.
I'm going to do the candy plan.
I'll join you.
What do you say we eat some macarons?
That sound good?
Hey, look, it's Circeus.
Hey there, big fella.
Oh, no.
If you're here, that means that psychopath's here, too, isn't he?
Ziya's training in the Divine Forest right now.
Did something happen?
Are you kidding me?
Or did you forget about all the stuff that went down with him and Nadinella last time?
She's a wreck to begin with, and now she's ten times worse.
Totally slipped my mind.
So what has she been doing, exactly?
What?
S-S-S-Saya, I'm going to c-c-kill you.
She skulks around like that all day.
It's like hearing the worst hip-hop DJ ever.
It's that bad, huh?
It is.
It's really not funny anymore.
If she sees him around, she's definitely going to gut him like a fish.
I'd heard she was upset.
I tried to cheer her up a bit, but she didn't want to listen to me.
I wonder if Ishtar could talk to her and try to smooth things out a little.
I'd keep her out of this.
I'm just afraid Seiya's going to get shanked.
Nadinella's strange, but she'd never do that.
And in the unlikely case she did, knowing that hero, he wouldn't even be phased.
Well, I don't really want to test that theory!
Not to mention go through all of this with him just to have him get killed by some side-eyeing golf goddess with a grudge!
I'm guessing she's not the best goddess to ask to help with my training, huh?
But what should I do instead?
If you stay here, it's all you can eat, can you?
Young man, I can sense that you have some dormant powers.
You mean the dragon god Metamorphosis?
They say if I can work hard enough, I'll be able to turn into a dragon.
Sounds like you have a seal.
If you want my help, I can release it for you.
For real? You could do that?
I'm all for learning new things, but that sounds like cheating to me.
I'm just teaching him the proper way to unlock a power he already possesses.
It's another form of training.
Okay, if you say it's fine, then knock yourself out.
Don't worry about me, Rista.
I'll just keep doing what I'm best at, which is shoveling candy.
Oh, I can see that you have some hidden talents as well.
I would be able to draw them out for you if you'd like.
Oh, really? If you think I could do something cool, then teach me.
Draw it out, drag it out, rip it out, whatever you need to do.
Ari is always the best for a good pick-me-up.
She even sees potential in Ailulu.
I'm sure she's right that Aranella is just a harmless wackadoodle.
But still, I think it's best for me to go and talk her down a little.
Hey, sweetie, it's your old friend Rista checking in.
Are you home?
I guess she's out.
Oh, she's out.
Out of her mind!
Starte, if you're back here, the matter means one thing.
Your tight-bodied friend is back here, too.
No, I came all by myself this time.
I don't know where he is.
Oh, is that true?
Really?
Oh, yeah, I haven't seen him in a while.
So, what do you need, anyway?
It's nothing.
Don't even worry about it.
Then why did you come in?
Oh, well, I was just looking for some decorating inspirations.
You've got such a unique style.
But I'm not sure I can pull this off as well.
Yeah?
Really?
Tanya!
So, how's it going?
She's done training me, but I should have it totally mastered by tomorrow.
Maybe sooner.
That's awesome, anyway!
Just make sure you don't set foot outside this forest and run into Adanella, got it?
And why should I be worried about that?
Just do what I'm asking you to do for once, okay?
I'll bring the shorties back here tomorrow and we'll leave!
You're way more annoying than usual today.
So, what crawled up your butt?
Please, I'm just asking that you stay here and try not to run into Adanella.
Do you really not know that she's standing right behind you?
I'm just asking that you're lying to me.
So, I decided to follow you here and find out the truth.
Hold on there, just take it easy!
I can explain everything!
Just calm down!
It's okay!
Now, I'll kill him.
Yes, I will.
He's gonna pay!
Oh no, that's the Adanella sword stance.
She did not come here to play.
Go on and draw your blade if you're man enough to fight against a woman who's ten times the warrior you are.
Hey, I know you're fine.
But how are you doing?
Long time no see.
What are you talking about?
You can't treat me like you did the other day and just expect me to act like nothing happened.
You gotta pay!
What is up with your hair?
Something the matter with it?
She's gonna pierce your spleen, you idiot!
You do own a comb, don't you?
S-s-stop touching me with your warm, manly hands like that.
Now isn't that better?
Hey!
Come on, Captain Battery Issues!
You-you...
I-I-I-I-I-I-I forgive you.
Eh?
What happened to all that psycho rage?
Did he pin it out of you?
I-I just can't help myself.
It's cliched, but I can't stay mad at someone so hot.
Adanella, I need to get back to my training.
You being here is distracting and it brings me down.
So hurry on out of here now.
Uh-uh-all right.
L-love you.
Wow, that's horrible.
I mean, he's hot, I get it, but have some self-respect.
Knowing that hero, he wouldn't even be fazed.
Yeah, she really called that one.
Maybe I'll get carried away.
Out of the way.
I'm training here.
Hmm.
Out of the way.
繋いだ糸
遠く細いけど輝いた絆
確かめた追いつけない
オラバラスライ
刻んでそっと
痛いな一歩
愛想のない大きな手のひら
心配
振り詰むなの
独り
愛のために
世界の鍵
本当の勇気は
In your hand
抱きしめるよ